Guide to the Gay Men's Health Crisis records
The New York Public Library. Manuscripts and Archives Division.
- Series IV. Client Services, 1982-1999, n.d.; 24 boxes
  - IV. A. Administrative Files, 1983-1994, n.d.; 9 boxes
    - Crisis Intervention Services, 1989-1990 (Box 97, Folder 11)
    - Crisis Intervention Team Handbook and Training Manuals, 1982-1985 (Box 97, Folder 12-13)
    - Crisis research, 1983-1984, n.d. (Box 97, Folder 14)
    - Department of Health
      - New York City, 1987-1989 (Box 98, Folder 1)
      - New York State, 1984-1985 (Box 98, Folder 2)
    - Development, 1986-1987 (Box 98, Folder 3)
    - Education Services memoranda, 1983-1987, n.d. (Box 98, Folder 4-5)
    - Financial advocacy, 1990-1991 (Box 98, Folder 6)
    - Financial aid advocacy, 1983-1987 (Box 98, Folder 7)
    - Financial policies and procedures, 1987 (Box 98, Folder 8)
    - Flyers, undated (Box 98, Folder 9)
    - Handouts, 1983-1987, n.d. (Box 98, Folder 10-11)
    - Hispanic AIDS Forum, 1985 (Box 98, Folder 12)
    - Hotline
      - Memoranda, 1983-1987 (Box 98, Folder 13)
      - Protocol, 1983-1984 (Box 99, Folder 1)
    - Human Resources Administration statistical report, 1984 (Box 99, Folder 2)
    - Human Services Management Institute, 1989 (Box 99, Folder 3)
    - Intake Department
      - General, 1984-1985, 1989 (Box 99, Folder 4)
      - Forms, 1984-1988 (Box 99, Folder 5)
      - Manual, 1984-1985, n.d. (Box 99, Folder 6)
      - Memoranda, 1983-1987 (Box 99, Folder 7)
      - Process, 1988 (Box 99, Folder 8)
    - Intake/Referral statistical reports
      - 1990 (Box 99, Folder 9-10)
      - 1991, n.d. (Box 100, Folder 1-2)
    - Interview program, 1983-1985 (Box 100, Folder 3)
    - Legal Aid, 1983-1987 (Box 100, Folder 4)
    - Lesbian AIDS Project, 1992 (Box 100, Folder 5)
    - Living with AIDS: A Practical Guide to New York City Resources, 1988-1993, 1997 (Box 100, Folder 6-10)
    - Lopez, Diego, 1983-1985 (Box 101, Folder 1)
    - Memoranda, 1984-1989, n.d. (Box 101, Folder 2-3)
    - Multiculturalism at GMHC, 1990, 1993, n.d (Box 101, Folder 4)
    - New Spanish publication review, 1991 (Box 101, Folder 5)
    - Occupational therapy proposal, 1988 (Box 101, Folder 6)
    - Ombudsman AIDS discrimination project, 1984-1985, n.d. (Box 101, Folder 7)
    - Organization chart, 1983 (Box 101, Folder 8)
    - Past and present challenges, 1991 (Box 101, Folder 9)
    - Patient committees, 1983-1986 (Box 101, Folder 10)
    - People of Color Resource Committee, 1988-1989 (Box 101, Folder 11)
    - Personnel policy, 1984-1987 (Box 101, Folder 12)
    - Planned Parenthood, 1988 (Box 101, Folder 13)
    - Policies and procudes manual, 1987-1988 (Box 102, Folder 1)
    - Program evaluation, undated (Box 102, Folder 2)
    - Public relations memoranda, 1983-1987 (Box 102, Folder 3)
    - Recreation Services Program
      - General, 1985-1986 (Box 102, Folder 4)
      - Activities record, 1987-1990 (Box 102, Folder 5-8)
      - Client questionnaires, undated (Box 102, Folder 9)
    - Research Review Board, 1984 (Box 102, Folder 10)
    - Resources, 1987-1990, n.d. (Box 103, Folder 1-2)
    - SAI-CFA volunteer needs, 1992 (Box 103, Folder 3)
    - Sing Sing AIDS Unit, undated (Box 103, Folder 4)
    - Staff meetings minutes, 1983-1987 (Box 103, Folder 5-10)
    - Student placement needs, 1992 (Box 103, Folder 11)
    - Supplemental Nutrition Assistance Program, 1988-1990 (Box 103, Folder 12)
    - Support groups, 1982, 1985-1987, n.d (Box 103, Folder 13)
    - Support services report, 1990-1991 (Box 104, Folder 1)
    - Supporting People with AIDS, 1988 (Box 104, Folder 2)
    - Therapeutic Recreation Program policy and procedure manual, 1989-1990 (Box 104, Folder 3)
    - Training rosters, 1985 (Box 104, Folder 4)
    - Training unit, undated (Box 104, Folder 5)
    - Village Nursing Home, 1985 (Box 104, Folder 6)
    - Volunteer manual, 1989 (Box 104, Folder 7)
    - Volunteer Office memoranda, 1984-1987 (Box 104, Folder 8)
    - Volunteer Training Program manual, 1988-1990 (Box 104, Folder 9)
    - Volunteers, 1986 (Box 104, Folder 10)
    - Weekly update, 1985-1986 (Box 104, Folder 11)
  - IV. B. Crisis Intervention Services, 1983-1997; 8 boxes
    Crisis Intervention Services administered the three crisis programs at GMHC:
    Buddy Program Crisis Intervention Workers Crisis Management Partners
    These services were generally the first a PWA received upon arriving at GMHC and provided emotional support and assistance with social services.
    The Buddy Program was one of the first services provided by GMHC, begun in 1982 as a formal program continuing the work of people helping their friends and lovers who were affected by AIDS. Buddies were volunteers who assisted PWAs with everyday tasks such as shopping, laundry, dog walking, as well as providing companionship. Team meetings were held at members' apartments and included accounts of what they had done the previous month with their client and reports on the client's mental and physical status, living situation, and any other particulars deemed important by the team member.
    The Crisis Intervention Worker (CIW) program evolved out of the Buddy Program. As more and more people became infected with AIDS and were turned away from hospitals or refused services from other agencies, Buddies started to act as intermediaries. GMHC soon divided the two areas of responsibility, leaving the Buddies to provide more emotional and practical support while the CIW handled social services issues for the client. The role of the CIW expanded over time to include peer counseling and to act as a liaison between the client, GMHC, and other agencies. The CIW generally worked with the client for a few weeks, while the Buddy would stay with the client as long as was needed.
    The Crisis Management Partner program began in 1985 and combined the roles of the Buddies and the Crisis Intervention Workers (CIW).
    This subseries contains the meeting minutes for the programs administered by the Crisis Intervention Services Department. The minutes reflect on an individual level the impact of the AIDS epidemic. They contain discussions of the problems encountered by volunteers seeking to help their clients; address methodology and the need for maintaining confidentiality; and consider the difficulties encountered assisting clients, and the psychological and emotional effects on the volunteers.
    - Buddy Program, 1983-1996, n.d.
      - Team Leaders and Captains, 1983-1989
        - 1983-1987 (Box 408, Folder 1-2)
        - 1988-1989 (Box 105, Folder 1)
      - Team #1, 1983-1996 (Box 105, Folder 2-7)
      - Team #2
        - 1984-1987 (Box 105, Folder 8)
        - 1988-1996 (Box 106, Folder 1-3)
      - Team #3, 1984-1996 (Box 106, Folder 4-7)
      - Team #4
        - 1985-1987 (Box 106, Folder 8-9)
        - 1988-1996 (Box 107, Folder 1-4)
      - Team #5, 1984-1996 (Box 107, Folder 5-8)
      - Team #6
        - 1986-1987 (Box 107, Folder 9-10)
        - 1988-1996 (Box 108, Folder 1-2)
      - Team #7, 1984-1996 (Box 108, Folder 3-9)
      - Team #8
        - 1985-1990 (Box 108, Folder 10)
        - 1991-1996, n.d. (Box 109, Folder 1)
      - Team #9, 1984, 1987-1996 (Box 109, Folder 2-7)
    - Crisis Intervention Workers, 1983-1997
      - Team #1
        - 1984-1990 (Box 109, Folder 8-9)
        - 1991-1996 (Box 110, Folder 1-2)
      - Team #2, 1984 (Box 110, Folder 3)
      - Team #3, 1984-1985 (Box 110, Folder 4)
      - Team #4, 1984-1985 (Box 110, Folder 5)
      - Team #5, 1984-1990 (Box 110, Folder 6)
      - Team #6
        - 1983-1993 (Box 110, Folder 7-9)
        - 1994-1997 (Box 111, Folder 1)
      - Team #7, 1984-1996 (Box 111, Folder 2-5)
      - Team #8, 1984-1994 (Box 111, Folder 6-7)
      - Team #10, 1984-1995 (Box 112, Folder 1-3)
      - Team #12, 1984-1985 (Box 112, Folder 4)
      - Team #13, 1984-1996 (Box 112, Folder 5-8)
      - Team #14
        - 1984-1988 (Box 112, Folder 9)
        - 1989-1996 (Box 113, Folder 1-2)
    - Crisis Management Partners, 1985-1996
      - Team #1, 1985-1996 (Box 113, Folder 3-6)
      - Team #2
        - 1985-1990 (Box 113, Folder 7-8)
        - 1991-1996 (Box 114, Folder 1-2)
      - Team #3, 1985-1996, n.d. (Box 114, Folder 3-7)
      - Team #5, 1989 (Box 114, Folder 8)
      - Team #9, 1994, n.d. (Box 114, Folder 9)
      - Team #13, 1994 (Box 114, Folder 10)
      - Miscellaneous meetings, 1985-1986, 1994 (Box 114, Folder 11)
  - IV. C. Nutrition Assessment Forms, 1993-1995; 7 boxes (Box 115-122)
    This subseries contains questionnaires completed by GMHC clients seeking nutrition counseling. These questionnaires include charts detailing what the client ate over the course of a day, medical tests they received, and weight gain/loss results.
- Series V. Communications Department, 1985-1997; 12.5 boxes
  The Communications Department (originally known as the Public Information Department) was responsible for the dissemination of public information on AIDS; press relations with GMHC; advocacy advertisement campaigns and policy issues for internal communications regarding clients, volunteers, and staff. Members of the department strove to ensure that stories on AIDS were reported accurately and sensitively. The department was also responsible for publishing the monthly News from GMHC, the bimonthly The Volunteer, and the annual reports which were sent to clients, volunteers, and donors.
  This subseries contains the Administrative Files of the Communications Department which consists of memoranda and reports for various departments within GMHC describing their programs. Communications and the Public Policy Department worked closely together and there are files within this subseries reflecting their collaboration. There are also lists of reporters and news sources with which GMHC had contact. The file entitled Media Reporting contains letters to editors of various newspapers and a paper on media coverage of AIDS before Rock Hudson's revelation that he had the disease.
  - Administrative assistant, 1993 (Box 123, Folder 1)
  - Adult children of Persons with AIDS, 1990 (Box 123, Folder 2)
  - Advertising, 1990-1993 (Box 123, Folder 3)
  - Advertorials, 1993 (Box 123, Folder 4)
  - AIDS Action Council, 1991-1993 (Box 123, Folder 5)
  - AIDS Awareness Day, 1992-1993 (Box 123, Folder 6)
  - AIDS in the workplace, 1990-1992 (Box 123, Folder 7)
  - AIDS Walk, 1992-1993 (Box 123, Folder 8)
  - Albany, Malkin and Ross, 1991-1992 (Box 123, Folder 9)
  - ANDY Awards, 1989 (Box 123, Folder 10)
  - Annual reports
    - 1991 (Box 123, Folder 11)
    - 1992-1993 (Box 124, Folder 1)
  - Association of the Bar of the City of New York, 1988-1989 (Box 124, Folder 2)
  - Benefit plan changes, 1992 (Box 124, Folder 3)
  - Berlin AIDS Conference (IXth International conference on AIDS), 1993 (Box 124, Folder 4)
  - Board of Directors, 1992-1993 (Box 124, Folder 5)
  - Boycott Colorado, 1993 (Box 124, Folder 6)
  - Brooklyn Historical Society exhibit on AIDS, 1991-1992 (Box 124, Folder 7)
  - Budget
    - 1989-1992 May (Box 124, Folder 8-12)
    - 1992 Jun-1994 (Box 125, Folder 1-2)
  - Building Study Committee, 1992-1993 (Box 125, Folder 3)
  - Cable show, 1985 (Box 125, Folder 4)
  - CARE Bill grants, 1992 (Box 125, Folder 5)
  - Client Programs, 1995-1996 (Box 125, Folder 6)
  - Client Services, 1990-1992 (Box 125, Folder 7)
  - Communications Coordinator, 1991 (Box 125, Folder 8)
  - Communications goals and planning, 1990-1991 (Box 125, Folder 9)
  - Communications survey, 1991 (Box 125, Folder 10)
  - Communities of color, 1993 (Box 125, Folder 11)
  - Corporate identity, 1991-1992 (Box 125, Folder 12)
  - Cuomo, Mario
    - Campaign, 1993 (Box 125, Folder 13)
    - Executive budget, 1992-1993 (Box 125, Folder 14)
  - Daily press interview requests
    - 1989 May-Aug 15 (Box 125, Folder 15)
    - 1989 Aug 16-1990, n.d. (Box 126, Folder 1-5)
  - Dance-A-Thon, 1992-1993 (Box 126, Folder 6)
  - Development Department
    - General, 1989-1993 (Box 126, Folder 7-10)
    - Corporate outreach and donors, 1991, 1996 (Box 127, Folder 1)
    - Direct mail, 1990-1992 (Box 127, Folder 2)
    - Donor survey, 1991 (Box 127, Folder 3)
    - Major donors, 1991 (Box 127, Folder 4)
  - Doctor's duty to disclose, 1991 (Box 127, Folder 5)
  - Drug development, 1991 (Box 127, Folder 6)
  - Duets, 1993 (Box 127, Folder 7)
  - Education Campaign, 1991-1992 (Box 127, Folder 8)
  - Education Department, 1989-1990 (Box 127, Folder 9-10)
  - Empire State Pride agenda, 1992-1993 (Box 127, Folder 11)
  - Eng, David, 1991-1994 (Box 127, Folder 12)
  - Executive Director, 1989-1990 (Box 127, Folder 13)
  - Fair share, 1992 (Box 127, Folder 14)
  - Fellowship program, 1991 (Box 127, Folder 15)
  - Finance and administration, 1991 (Box 127, Folder 16)
  - Financial advocacy, 1989-1990 (Box 127, Folder 17)
  - fuel, 1995 (Box 127, Folder 18)
  - Gay community, 1989-1991 (Box 127, Folder 19)
  - Geto, Ethan, 1992 (Box 128, Folder 1)
  - Giles, Patrick, 1990-1993, n.d. (Box 128, Folder 2)
  - GMHC Facts, 1994-1997 (Box 128, Folder 3)
  - GMHC Friends, 1995 (Box 128, Folder 4)
  - GMHC news releases, 1988-1996 (Box 128, Folder 5)
  - Gould, Douglas, 1990-1994 (Box 128, Folder 6-8)
  - Grant, Louis, 1990-1991 (Box 128, Folder 9)
  - Graphics, 1991 (Box 128, Folder 10)
  - Guantanamo advertisement, 1993 (Box 128, Folder 11)
  - Hansell, David, 1991-1992 (Box 128, Folder 12)
  - HIV Advocacy Group, 1993 (Box 129, Folder 1-2)
  - HIV Immigration Ban, 1993 (Box 129, Folder 3)
  - Housing Feasibility Study, 1992 (Box 129, Folder 4)
  - Johnson, Magic, 1991-1992 (Box 129, Folder 5)
  - Katoff, Lew, 1992 (Box 129, Folder 6)
  - Kaynal, Philip M., 1992-1993 (Box 129, Folder 7)
  - Latino advertising, 1993 (Box 129, Folder 8)
  - Legal Services, 1989-1991 (Box 129, Folder 9)
  - Lesbian AIDS Project, 1990-1993 (Box 129, Folder 10)
  - Lesbian and Gay Film Festival, 1993 (Box 129, Folder 11)
  - Letters to the Editor, 1992-1993 (Box 129, Folder 12)
  - Levy, Jeffrey, 1989 (Box 129, Folder 13)
  - Living legacy, 1993 (Box 129, Folder 14)
  - Lugliani, Greg, 1992-1993 (Box 129, Folder 15)
  - Management Team meetings
    - 1992 (Box 129, Folder 16)
    - 1993 (Box 130, Folder 1)
  - March on Washington
    - General, 1993 (Box 130, Folder 2-3)
    - Homophobia Kills bus shelter poster, 1993
  - Margitich, Mike, 1992 (Box 130, Folder 4)
  - Mayoral Forum on AIDS/HIV in New York City, 1989 (Box 130, Folder 5)
  - Media reporting on AIDS, 1986-1987, n.d. (Box 130, Folder 6)
  - Monthly reports, 1993 (Box 130, Folder 7)
  - Morning Party, 1993 (Box 130, Folder 8)
  - Mothers' Voices, 1992 (Box 130, Folder 9)
  - Multiculturalism, 1992-1993 (Box 130, Folder 10)
  - Music for Life, 1990-1993 (Box 130, Folder 11)
  - National Coalition for Children with HIV/AIDS and Their Families, 1989-1991 (Box 130, Folder 12)
  - New York City Commission on human Rights, 1993 (Box 130, Folder 13)
  - New York City Council, 1991-1992 (Box 131, Folder 1)
  - New York City Mayoral race, 1993 (Box 131, Folder 2)
  - New York Times Editorial Board, 1990 (Box 131, Folder 3)
  - 121 West 20th Street, 1991-1992 (Box 131, Folder 4)
  - Oral History Project, undated (Box 131, Folder 5)
  - Other organizations
    - General, 1989-1992, n.d. (Box 131, Folder 6)
    - Association for Drug Abuse and Treatment (ADAPT), 1990 (Box 131, Folder 7)
    - Gay and Lesbian Alliance Against Defamation (GLAAD), 1989-1990 (Box 131, Folder 8)
  - People of Color, 1988-1992, n.d. (Box 131, Folder 9-10)
  - Policy Department
    - General, 1989-1992, n.d. (Box 131, Folder 11-12)
    - Action alerts, 1990 (Box 131, Folder 13)
    - Current, 1992 (Box 132, Folder 1)
    - Priorities, 1991 (Box 132, Folder 2)
  - Press conferences, 1989-1991 (Box 132, Folder 3-4)
  - Print media
    - General, 1989-1991, n.d. (Box 132, Folder 5)
    - New York Times
      - New York Times (Box 132, Folder 6)
      - New York Times (Box 132, Folder 7)
  - Program, Policy and Communications Group, 1992-1993 (Box 132, Folder 8)
  - Program review, 1993 (Box 132, Folder 9)
  - Publications coordinator, 1993 (Box 132, Folder 10)
  - Publications of GMHC, 1995-1996, n.d. (Box 132, Folder 11)
  - Puerto Rican Day Parade, 1993 (Box 132, Folder 12)
  - Radio, 1989 (Box 132, Folder 13)
  - Relapse, 1990 (Box 132, Folder 14)
  - Restructuring, 1991-1993 (Box 132, Folder 15)
  - Retkin, Randye S., 1991 (Box 133, Folder 1)
  - Richardson, Jeff, 1993 (Box 133, Folder 2)
  - Roper poll update, 1991-1992 (Box 133, Folder 3)
  - Segmentation study, 1993 (Box 133, Folder 4)
  - Sock advertisement, 1992 (Box 133, Folder 5)
  - Soref, Jeff, 1992 (Box 133, Folder 6)
  - Space, 1991 (Box 133, Folder 7)
  - Spingarn, Ronald, 1993 (Box 133, Folder 8)
  - Stadtlander's Pharmacy, 1993 (Box 133, Folder 9)
  - Staff Caucus, 1989-1993 (Box 133, Folder 10)
  - Staff meetings, 1992-1993 (Box 133, Folder 11)
  - Staff memoranda, 1988-1996 (Box 133, Folder 12-13)
  - State of AIDS in New York, 1991-1993 (Box 133, Folder 14)
  - Story ideas, 1990, n.d. (Box 134, Folder 1)
  - Strategic plan, 1991-1992 (Box 134, Folder 2-3)
  - Sweeney, Timothy J., 1989-1993 (Box 134, Folder 4-5)
  - Tat Inhibitor, 1993 (Box 134, Folder 6)
  - Television, 1989-1991, n.d. (Box 134, Folder 7)
  - Torres, Gabriel, 1989, n.d. (Box 134, Folder 8)
  - Unionization at GMHC, 1993 (Box 134, Folder 9)
  - United for AIDS Action, 1991-1992 (Box 135, Folder 1)
  - V.I.P. list updates, 1992 (Box 135, Folder 2)
  - The Volunteer, 1990-1992, n.d. (Box 135, Folder 3-4)
  - Volunteers, 1989-1992 (Box 135, Folder 5-6)
  - Weeks, Natalie, 1990 (Box 135, Folder 7)
  - World AIDS Day Coalition, 1989-1992 (Box 135, Folder 8)
  - Wrap It Up event, 1993 (Box 135, Folder 9)
- Series VI. Development Department, 1982-1998, n.d.; 15.25 boxes
  The Development Department was responsible for raising the majority of GMHC's funding through direct mail, foundation and governmental funding, donors, and special events. The department sought to raise most of its funds from its special events, rather than be dependant on government programs. The special events created by GMHC included circuses, dance-a-thons, the AIDS Walk, art auctions, the Morning Party, and many others.
  This series is divided into three subseries: Administrative Files; Special Events; and the records of Patricia Evert who served as Assistant Director of Development and Special Events Director. Audiovisual materials associate with these records can be found in Series XVI.B.2.
  - VI. A. Administrative Files, 1982, 1987, 1990-1995, n.d; 2 boxes
    This subseries contains correspondence, memoranda, reports, and minutes of the Development Department. Included are memoranda on the capital campaigns conducted by GMHC and correspondence with donors.
    - 10th Anniversary Campaign, 1991 (Box 135, Folder 10)
    - AIDS Institute funding request, 1990-1994 (Box 135, Folder 11)
    - Americans with Disabilities Act, 1993 (Box 135, Folder 12)
    - Board of Directors, 1993-1994 (Box 135, Folder 13)
    - Budget themes, 1992-1993 (Box 135, Folder 14)
    - By-laws, 1991 (Box 135, Folder 15)
    - Capital Campaign, 1988-1989 (Box 135, Folder 16)
    - Certificate of incorporation, 1982 (Box 135, Folder 17)
    - Corporate gifts policy, 1994 (Box 135, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence, 1990-1995 (Box 135, Folder 19)
    - Deaf AIDS Project
      - 1991 (Box 135, Folder 20)
      - 1992 (Box 136, Folder 1)
    - Development Committee, 1991-1993 (Box 136, Folder 2)
    - Equal employment opportunity, 1992-1993 (Box 136, Folder 3)
    - Foundation letters and proposals, 1993 (Box 136, Folder 4)
    - Foundation tracking, 1993 (Box 136, Folder 5)
    - GMHC budget, 1993-1995 (Box 136, Folder 6-7)
    - GMHC building campaign, 1993, n.d. (Box 136, Folder 8)
    - Hotline counseling at GMHC, 1994, n.d. (Box 136, Folder 9)
    - Housing Feasibility Study, 1992 (Box 136, Folder 10)
    - Kresge Foundation, 1993 (Box 136, Folder 11)
    - Management Team meetings, 1992-1993 (Box 136, Folder 12)
    - Memoranda, 1992-1994, n.d. (Box 136, Folder 13)
    - New headquarters, 1987 (Box 136, Folder 14)
    - Operations and Procedures manual, 1993 (Box 136, Folder 15)
    - Photographs, 1987, n.d. (Box 136, Folder 16)
    - Program Committee, 1993-1994 (Box 136, Folder 17)
    - Program review, 1993 (Box 136, Folder 18)
    - Russell, Michelle and Richard Jasper prospect letters, 1992-1993 (Box 137, Folder 1)
    - Staff directory, undated (Box 137, Folder 2)
    - Strategic Planning Task Force/Mission statement, 1992-1993 (Box 137, Folder 3)
    - A Study of Contributors and Potential Contributors to the Gay Men's Health Crisis, 1988 (Box 137, Folder 4)
    - Substance Use Services, 1993, n.d. (Box 137, Folder 5)
  - VI. B. Events, 1984-1995, n.d.; 12.5 boxes
    This subseries contains correspondence, memoranda, minutes, notes, photographs, and programs related to the special fundraising events conducted by the Development Department. Included in these files are invitations, programs, and posters from GMHC's first fundraisers Showers, the Circus, and the World's Toughest Rodeo. Later events such as the various Art Auctions and Dance-A-Thons contain memoranda and minutes from planning meetings that document the development of these events.
    - AIDS Walk
      - General, 1987-1989, 1993-1994 (Box 137, Folder 6-7)
      - Posters, 1986-1996 (Box XX-14)
    - Angels on Ice
      - Advertisement sales, 1994 (Box 137, Folder 8)
      - Bulk mail, 1994 (Box 137, Folder 9)
      - Composers, 1994 (Box 137, Folder 10)
      - Contracts, 1994 (Box 137, Folder 11)
      - Correspondence, 1994 (Box 137, Folder 12)
      - Cossitt, Edwin, 1993-1994 (Box 137, Folder 13)
      - Designers, 1994 (Box 137, Folder 14)
      - Financial reports, 1994 (Box 137, Folder 15)
      - Graphics, 1994 (Box 137, Folder 16)
      - Ground transportation, 1994 (Box 138, Folder 1)
      - Ice Theatre of New York, 1994 (Box 138, Folder 2)
      - In kind, 1994 (Box 138, Folder 3)
      - Invitation, 1994 (Box 138, Folder 4)
      - Memoranda, 1993-1994 (Box 138, Folder 5-6)
      - Palm, Michael D., 1994 (Box 138, Folder 7)
      - Press, 1993-1994 (Box 138, Folder 8)
      - Program, 1994 (Box 138, Folder 9)
      - Radio, 1994 (Box 138, Folder 10)
      - Recanati, Michael, 1994 (Box 138, Folder 11)
      - Rosenberg, Nancy, 1994 (Box 138, Folder 12)
      - Skaters
        - A-G, 1994 (Box 138, Folder 13-15)
        - H-Z, Miscellaneous, 1994 (Box 139, Folder 1-6)
      - Special events fundraising, undated (Box 139, Folder 7)
      - Sponsors, 1994 (Box 139, Folder 8)
      - Thank you, 1994 (Box 139, Folder 9)
      - Tickets, 1994 (Box 139, Folder 10)
      - Timeline, 1994 (Box 139, Folder 11)
      - Tisch, Joan and Preston Robert Tisch, 1994 (Box 139, Folder 12)
    - Arista
      - Budget negotiations
        - 1988-1989 (Box 139, Folder 13)
        - 1990 (Box 140, Folder 1)
      - Contracts, 1988-1990 (Box 140, Folder 2)
      - Financials, 1988-1990 (Box 140, Folder 3)
      - General file, 1989-1990 (Box 140, Folder 4)
      - Gifts and thank yous, 1990 (Box 140, Folder 5)
      - National AIDS Network, 1990 (Box 140, Folder 6)
      - Press clippings, 1990 (Box 140, Folder 7)
      - Printed matter, 1990 (Box 140, Folder 8)
      - Program book, 1990 (Box 140, Folder 9)
      - Public relations, 1989-1990 (Box 140, Folder 10)
      - Seating, 1990 (Box 140, Folder 11)
      - Steering Committee, 1989-1990 (Box 141, Folder 1)
      - Steinberg party, 1990 (Box 141, Folder 2)
      - Thank you letters, 1990 (Box 141, Folder 3)
      - Ticket orders, 1989-1990 (Box 141, Folder 4)
      - Underwriting, 1990 (Box 141, Folder 5)
    - Art Auctions
      - 1984 Auction (Box 141, Folder 6)
      - 1985 Auction
        - General, 1985 (Box 141, Folder 7)
        - Advertising, 1985 (Box 141, Folder 8)